威尔 · 森特斯: 布雷登，请讲。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Braydon,
go ahead Braydon.
演讲者2: 所以如果我们试图使用存储网络数据的数据
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: So if we're trying to use
the data storing data from the network
如果你在 JavaScript 中有一行代码，在 global。
request, how does it if you have a line
of code in the JavaScript, in the global.
它怎么知道什么时候可以访问这些信息？
How does it know when it
can kinda access that?
威尔 · 森塔斯: 在现实的幕后,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Behind
the scenes in reality,
这么高的价值实际上从来没有填写。
this high value is never
filled in actually.
直到所有的全球代码完成运行，所以我们甚至不能访问它在那里
Until all global codes finish running, so
we can't even get access to it at that
在找到之前，我们只能从前门进入。
point until we have,
we only get access to it from the front.
那样的话，我的意思是这和回调模式不同，对吗？
And then that way, I mean that different
from the callback model, right?
你只能从我们添加的函数中访问,
You only get access to from
the function that we add,
因为我们不想有一种语言。
we also triggered because we just
don't want to have a language.
我们可以去的地方
Where we can go and
试着接触一些东西，但我们不知道它是否在那里。
try and get access to stuff and we don't
know if it's gonna be there or not.
所以我们不会在幕后自动填充,
So we don't actually fill that in
behind the scenes automatically,
直到所有的全球代码运行完毕。
until all global codes finish running.
好的，在实践中，这有一个小的结果。
Okay, in practice that
has a small consequence.
但是这和我给你们展示的方式有点不同
But it's slightly different to the way I
sort of showed you here where we sort of
暗示它在那一刻被填满。
imply it gets filled in
here at that moment.
但实际上是在最后一刻,
But in reality it's at
the very last minute,
在我们开始排队之前。
before we start going through the queues.
这不会带来任何后果。
That has no consequences in terms of.
我们不会运行这些函数直到它被填满,
We don't run these functions
until it's filled in,
直到我们完成所有的全球代码，所以没有后果。
until we finish all the global
code anyway so no consequences.
马克？
Mark?
演讲者2: 我正在思考如何恰当地表达这句话。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: I'm trying to think
of how to phrase this properly.
维尔 · 森坦斯: 你想休息一会儿吗？
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Do you
want to take one sec?
演讲者2: 我可以试试。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: I can try.
如果它是一个打印 hello 当浏览器有它，是一个引用全局打印 hello。
If it's a print hello when the browser has
it, is a reference to global print hello.
不是打印你好本身。
Is not print hello itself.
威尔 · 森坦斯: 是的，我们不会在网页浏览器中复制
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Yeah, we're not
taking into the web browser a copy of
函数。
the function.
我们只是给出一个内存中的引用，这个函数，是的。
We're just giving a reference back
to in memory, this function, yeah.
演讲者2: 可以打印 hello，在你点击的时候要考虑到
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Could print hello, take
into consideration by the time you hit
成本文本的东西从全局内存的另一个参数？
the cost text something another
parameter from global memory?
或者一定是可以的。
Or is it must have been can.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 这很难做到，因为。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: It will
be hard to do so, because.
演讲者2: 是的 威尔 · 森特斯: 等等,
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Yeah.
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Hold on,
谁要把父母的照片印出来？
who's putting the parenths on print?
你好，我们在做吗，是的。
Hello, are we doing it, yeah.
我们要把指纹印出来吗？
Are we putting prints on print?
- 喂?-没有。
Hello?
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: No.
威尔 · 森坦斯: 没有 JavaScript 在做这件事。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: No JavaScript's
doing it.
如果我们不把品牌放在我们如何插入任何争论？
If we're not putting brands on
how do we insert any arguments?
我们必须依靠知道。
We have to rely on knowing.
这是一个非常好的观点，在这里是最重要的。
And this is a really good point,
the most making here.
这意味着我们必须知道，比如,
It means we have to know like,
for example,
你可以换个方式回答，马克，等等。
you might answer a different way mark,
hold on.
是否有两个参数传递给我，这两个参数都是关于显示
Could I have two arguments passed to me
that's all about display the function that
得到它的第一个输入。
gets its first input.
返回的数据好像我只能有两个参数。
Data that comes back as if I could only
be have that expect two arguments.
现在我得走了
Now, I've got to go and
看看 web 浏览器的功能到底是怎样的
look at exactly how the feature of
the web browser that this function is
当功能网页浏览器完成工作时，将自动触发。
going to be auto triggered when
the feature web browser finishes work.
它是如何期待网页浏览器和
How it's expecting how the web browser and
疾病的希望，希望这一功能能够得到展示。
the promise of disease expecting
this function to be laid out.
我该去哪里找规则呢？
Where do I go to find
the rules about that?
我在哪里才能知道浏览器是如何期待这个功能的
Where am I gonna find out how
the browser is expecting the function
那将是自动运行。
that will be auto run.
什么时候它的工作完成是会工作，它会采取什么投入？
When its work is done is gonna work and
what inputs it's gonna take?
我怎么才能知道呢？
How do I find that out, everybody?
无论是一个网站。
Whether it's a website.
讲者二: 多媒体网络 威尔 · 森塔斯: 关闭
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: MDN.
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Shutting
就是这个 MDN。
the MDN, exactly.
Mdn 有一个所有这些特性的列表。
MDN has got a list of all these features.
他们不称这些外观函数。
They don't call these facade functions.
他们称之为 API 是一个它代表的接口是任何功能或
They call them API is a it stands for
interface that is any functionality or
通常数据不在我的世界里，而是在别人的世界里，我与之交互。
often data that's not in my world, but
in someone else's and I interface with it.
这些是我的标签，我可以通过它们进行交互
These are my labels by which
I can interface interact with
这个外面的世界。
this outside world.
这和你说的有点关系，马克,
That being said slightly related to
what you're saying, Mark, though,
假设我在执行和其他函数中设置了超时调用。
is suppose I set timeout call inside
the execution and other function.
它想使用一些来自执行上下文的数据。
And it wanted to use some of the data
from that execution context.
等到印刷版 hello 运行的时候它已经在 global 上运行了,
Well, by the time print hello runs,
it runs in global,
设置超时的执行上下文已经消失,
that execution context in which
set timeout with set up has gone,
所有的数据都没了除非...-扬声器2: 背包。
and all its data's gone, unless the-
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Backpack.
威尔 · 森特斯: Backpack，确切地说，print hello 有一个链接到它周围的所有地方
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Backpack, exactly, print
hello has a link to all its surrounding
可以用在里面的记忆，太棒了，太神奇了。
memory that could ever be used in it,
pretty awesome, that's pretty amazing.
好的，我们还有一个，是的，杰森，拜托？
Okay, we had another one,
yeah, Jason, please?
演讲者2: (咳嗽)对不起，这个例子至少给我们留下了印象
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: [COUGH] Excuse me, so the
example at least gives us the impression
微任务队列要么是第一个,
that the micro-task queue
is either first in,
最后，它优先使用的地方——威尔 · 森坦斯: 好问题。
last out, where it's used preferentially-
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Good question.
扬声器2: 根据你将要接到的电话类型，你会接到哪里
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Where you've got depending
on the type of call you're gonna get
排队。
a queue.
我怀疑微任务其实是有自己的发明循环的
My suspicion is the micro-task is
actually has its own invent loop
威尔 · 森塔斯: 因为，不,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Because well no,
这个活动需要处理。
the event needs handling.
让我们来讨论一下微任务队列单词与 Jason 的单词之间的关系
Let's talk a bit about how the micro
task queue words relates to what Jason's
问他们。
asking them.
如果不是真正有趣呢？
What if isn't really interesting?
所以对于承诺对象，我可以直接创建一个。
So it turns out with promise objects,
I can just create one directly.
我不需要通过获取自动创建它,
I don't need to have it
automatically created by fetch,
我只能说创造一个。
I can actually just say create one.
如果我说解决这个问题，也就是说在那一刻，在那一行代码中。
If I then say resolve that, that is to
say in that line of code in that moment.
让它自动完成
Have it automatically complete and
我可以控制这个功能。
have its function at that I
can control that function.
我们可以通过抓取来做到这点。
We can do that with fetch.
因为获取在这里处理关系，但是
Because fetch is handling
the relationship here, but
如果我制作了自己的承诺对象，那么我就可以有附加的功能。
if I make my own promise object, then I
can have the function attached to it.
我可以直接将它插入到微任务队列中
I can directly myself have it stuck
into the microtask queue by having
承诺对象的值属性更新并完整。
the value property of that promise
object updated and complete.
并自动触发该函数在微任务队列中运行。
And automatically trigger the function
to run in the microtask queue.
这里有一个非常有趣的场景。
Here's a really interesting scenario.
如果当我运行微任务中的函数时
If when I'm running the function
that was in my microtask
队列显示，如果在那里面。
queue that was displayed,
If inside of there.
我创建了一个全新的承诺对象，它的相关功能
I create a brand new promise object
that its associated function
当我在里面展示的时候。
while I was inside display.
这个承诺对象完成了，因为我直接告诉它,
That promise object completed
because I told it to directly,
相关的函数将插入到微任务队列的后端
the associated function will be stuck into
the backend of microtask queue while I'm
还在里面展示。
still inside display.
威尔 · 森坦斯: 这是一个真正的
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Here's a really
有趣的情况可能会发生。
interesting situation
that can happen then.
我可以在微任务队列的后面填充更多内容
I can be filling in the back of
the micro task queue with more
当我还在里面展示的时候就可以运行了。
functions while I'm still inside display.
事件循环非常有趣
And the event loop is interesting and
如何与微任务队列交互是一个非常非常大的奖励。
how it interacts with the micro task
queue is a very, very big bonus sort of.
如果你想知道节点的硬件部分，我们会进入一些更详细的内容。
If you go to if you want to know the node
hard parts, we go into some more detail.
他们太担心这个了。
They're worried too much about this.
但我感觉如果我想，我在里面展示和
But I am feeling if I want
I'm inside display and
在这后面填充新的功能。
filling in new functions behind here.
他们自己也在建立一个新的功能。
And they themselves
are building a new functions.
这些都是新的函数，几乎是递归的。
And then those are pretty new
function almost recursively.
我将永远不会离开微剂量队列，因为事件循环
I will never leave the microdose
queue because the event loop
总是在调用堆栈上执行。
will always take in and
execute on the call stack.
它总是会回到过去
It will always go back and
在进入回调队列之前检查微任务。
check the microtask before it
moves on to the callback queue.
这与进入回调队列后完成所有任务的回调队列是不同的
That is in distinction to the callback
queue which once it enters does all
里面的东西，然后再转一圈。
the stuff in there and
then moves round again.
一旦进入微任务队列,
The microtask queue once it enters,
如果你在后面加油，就别想离开。
if you are refilling in the back,
you ain't leaving it.
在 Node 中，您得到了所谓的饿死回调队列。
You get what's called starve
the callback queue and in Node.
这一点特别重要，因为您希望，您知道，生产应用程序。
This is particularly important because you
want to, you know, production application.
这就是为什么在使用时要小心谨慎
And this is why there's some
caution around around using
过程下一滴答方法。
the process next tick method.
在这个队列中插入一些东西
Which sticks stuff in this queue, and
可以递归地使您无法处理来自用户的请求。
can recursively starve you handling
your requests from your users.
瓦朗斯我的话题，但去看节点哈珀的，你感兴趣的，但
Valence I topic, but go watch the Node
Harper's, you're interested in that, but
有趣的是，它们的行为方式略有不同。
it's an interesting nature that these
are behaving slightly differently.
正如杰森暗示的那样，还有一个布雷登，是不是
Just as Jason was hinting,
there was one more Brayden, was it or
是 Peter 还是 Kayla？
was it Peter or Kayla?
丹，是丹，说吧，丹。
Dan, it was Dan, yeah, go ahead, Dan.
扬声器2: 是的，当你可能已经提到这一点，但是。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Yeah when you may
have already mentioned this, but.
什么项目进入微任务队列，什么项目进入。
What items go into the microtask queue and
what items go into.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 很好，很好。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Great, great point.
让我们把话说清楚。
Let's just be really, really clear.
任何通过这两个分支之一连接到承诺对象的函数
Any function that is attached to a promise
object by one of these two prongs for
存储函数。
stored functions.
这就给了 add 一个 promise 对象，我们用它们给它附加了一个函数。
Which gives add a promise object we
attach a function to it using them.
这些功能都会进入到你的微任务中。
Those functions all go
into the micro-task you.
任何直接传递给 facade 函数的函数都会触发 web
Any function that's passed in directly
to a facade function that triggers a web
浏览器功能，你看到的参考，链接到这里的功能。
browser feature you see the reference
that link to the function down here.
这些功能，当他们完成或
Those functions when they complete or
对不起，当后台任务的计时器完成这个函数回调。
sorry when the background task the timer
completes this function callback.
所以我们必须进入 MDN
So we have to go into MDN and
看，我们特殊的正面功能，能触发背景中的东西吗？
see, does our particular facade function
that trigger stuff in the background?
它包含一个函数吗？
Does it take in a function?
那个会进入回调队伍吗？
That one's going to go
into the callback queue?
或者它会返回去提出一个承诺对象
Or does it return out to
promed a promise object and
他们抛出的背景，但没有抛出一个函数在这里。
they toss to the background but
doesn't throw a function down here.
Promise 对象上的关联函数，即-微任务队列。
The associative function on the promise
object, that- microtask queue.
好的，亲爱的。
Okay, sweet.